Finding aid to the Classes of 1921-1930 records CA.MS.01019
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1921-1930 records
1917-2002
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1921.
CA.MS.01019
130.437 linear feet (200 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
A portion of these materials were transferred to College Archives in 14 accessions between 1998 and 2017. Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Content Description
The Classes of 1921-1930 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College -- Students -- History -- Sources; Smith College. Class of 1922.; Smith College. Class of 1923.; Smith College. Class of 1924.; Smith College. Class of 1925.; Smith College. Class of 1926.; Smith College. Class of 1927; Smith College. Class of 1928.; Smith College. Class of 1929.; Smith College. Class of 1930.; Pierpont, Grace, Class of 1924; Brown, Margaret Pauline; Green, Helen, Class of 1926; Sullivan, Lillian
- Class of 1921 records, 1917-1991; 11.833 linear feet (18 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1921 was the forty-third graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1921 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1921, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, Treasurer's records, pamphlets, and other memorabilia. Individual biographical files often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  They also contain a photograph album whose creator, Lilian Sullivan, is of unknown relationship to Smith College, but which contains a large number of photographs of the Smith College campus from around 1919-1921.
  - Commencement, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photos, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1917 (Box 1937, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Grind, 1917 (Box 1937, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1917-1918 (Box 1937, Folder 6)
  - Gift, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1917-1921 (Box 1937, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Day, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day-Photos, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1920 (Box 1937, Folder 11)
  - Class Letters, 1957-1991 (Box 1937, Folder 12)
  - Organization, 1917 (Box 1937, Folder 13)
  - Class President's Scrapbook, 1921-1968 (Box 1937.2)
  - Reunions, 1926 (Box 1938, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1936 (Box 1938, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 1938, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1938, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 1938, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1951-1956 (Box 1938, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 1938, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 1938, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 1938, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1976 (Box 1938, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1981 (Box 1938, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1985-1986 (Box 1938, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1991 (Box 1938, Folder 13)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1938, Folder 14)
  - Class Scrapbooks- General, A-Br (Box 1938.3)
  - Class Scrapbooks- Bu-L (Box 1938.4)
  - Class Scrapbooks- M-Z (Box 1938.5)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 14)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 16)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1937, Folder 17)
  - Class Supper, 1921 (Box 1937, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer-Annual Records, 1971-1985 (Box 1937.1, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer-Bequests, 1973-1985 (Box 1937.1, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer-Class Dues, 1977-1985 (Box 1937.1, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer-Alumnae Council, 1972-1981 (Box 1937.1, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer-50th Reunion, 1971 (Box 1937.1, Folder 6)
  - Treasury Records-Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 1937.1, Folder 7)
  - Records of War Work (WWII), 1946 (Box 1937.1, Folder 1)
  - Individuals A-L (Box 1939)
  - Individuals M-R (Box 1940)
  - Individuals S-Z (Box 1941)
  - Anthony, Helen Van Zile (photo album) (Box 1942)
  - Apted, Isadore Button (photograph albums) (Box 1942.1)
  - Frazier, Helen (photo album) (Box 1944.2)
  - Gould, Margaret Sylvester (memorabilia book) (Box 1944.4)
  - Graves, Elizabeth Waterman: scrapbook (Box 1944.3)
  - Green, Helen (memorabilia book) (Box 1943)
  - Hutchinson, Ruth (memorabilia book) (Box 1944.5)
  - Kirsten, Martha Amalia (correspondence, diary) (Box 1944)
  - Lillian Sullivan photograph album of Smith College, around 1919-1921; 2017-A-0155; .25 linear feet (1 half document box) (Box 1)
    Photograph album of Lillian Sullivan, unknown connection to Smith College, but with extensive images of the College around 1919-1921.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Donated by Sharlene Van Rooy, unknown connection to Lillian Sullivan
  - Ward, Marian (photo album) (Box 1944.1)
- Class of 1922 records, 1918-1992; 8.375 linear feet (13 containers)
  The Class of 1922 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1922, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  The Class of 1922 was the forty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  - Clippings, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1918 (Box 1945, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1918-1919 (Box 1945, Folder 7)
  - Fund Letters, 1948-1964 (Box 1945, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1918-1922 (Box 1945, Folder 9)
  - History, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1922 (Box 1945, Folder 12)
  - Junior Frolic, 1921 (Box 1945, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1921 (Box 1945, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1944-1976 (Box 1945, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1945, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1923 (Box 1945, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1927 (Box 1945, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1932 (Box 1945, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 1945, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1945, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 1945, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 1945, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 1945, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 1945, Folder 25)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 1945, Folder 26)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 1946, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1977-1982 (Box 1946, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 1946, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 1946, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records, undated (Box 1946, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1922 (Box 1946, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1922 (Box 1946, Folder 7)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1922 (Box 1946, Folder 8)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1946, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1920 (Box 1946, Folder 10)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1920 (Box 1946, Folder 11)
  - Step Sings, 1922 (Box 1946, Folder 12)
  - Class Supper, 1922 (Box 1946, Folder 13)
  - Year Book, 1922 (Box 1946, Folder 14)
  - Individuals A-G (Box 1947)
  - Individuals H-L (Box 1947.1)
  - Individuals M-Z (Box 1948)
  - Adams, Marjorie Bradford (memorabilia book) (Box 1953.1)
  - Chilton, Eleanor Carroll (photo album, poems, plays) (Box 1949)
  - Clark, Carita Louise (scrapbook) (Box 1953.3)
  - Crandall, Marjorie Lyle (correspondence, class notes) (Box 1950)
  - Cullinan, Margaret Anne (correspondence, class notes) (Box 1951)
  - Irwin, Ruth Elizabeth (scrapbook) (Box 1951.1)
  - Marshall, Elisabeth (music scores) (Box 1953.2)
  - Smith, Harriet Maria (memorabilia book) (Box 1953.2)
  - Smith, Catherine (memorabilia book) (Box 1952)
  - Wilder, Florence Caroline (memorabilia book, misc.) (Box 1953)
- Class of 1923 records, 1919-1988; 12.333 linear feet (17 containers)
  - Campus Catechism, undated (Box 1955, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1919 (Box 1955, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Grind, 1919 (Box 1955, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1919-1920 (Box 1955, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1919-1923 (Box 1955, Folder 8)
  - History, 1919-1923 (Box 1955, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 11)
  - Last Chapel, 1923 (Box 1955, Folder 12)
  - Class Letters, 1954-1976 (Box 1955, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1924 (Box 1955, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1926 (Box 1955, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1928 (Box 1955, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 1955, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 1955, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1943 (Box 1955, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1955, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 1955, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 1955, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1973-1978 (Box 1955, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1983-1988 (Box 1955, Folder 24)
  - Secretary's Book, 1921-1983 (Box 1955, Folder 25)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 2)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1956, Folder 3)
  - Sophomore-Senior Banquet, 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 4)
  - Songs, 1923 (Box 1956, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files (Box 1955.1)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files (Box 1955.2)
  - Individuals A-B (Box 1955)
  - Individuals C-Z (Box 1957)
  - Bancroft, Caroline (post grad) (Box 1960)
  - Bleakly, Edith Bryan (memorabilia book) (Box 1962.1)
  - Borton, Eleanor Brown (photo album) (Box 1962.2)
  - Brown, Margaret Pauline, ex-class of 1923 (correspondence), May 1919-June 1920; 2017-A-0160; Brown, Margaret Pauline; Goolsby, N. Anne; .25 linear feet (1 half document box) (Box 1)
    Correspondence from Margaret Pauline Brown, ex-Class of 1923, to her parents. Also includes letters from the college, letters from friends, tuition bills, room reservations, photographs, and pressed leaves.
    Goolsby, N. Anne
  - Cary, Madeleine (memorabilia albums) (Box 1958)
  - Clark, Mary Elizabeth (scrapbook) (Box 1962.3)
  - Conklin, Miriam (Box 1959)
  - Conklin, Miriam (scrapbook) (Box 1962.4)
  - Ford, Frances Lavinia (memorabilia book) (Box 1962.5)
  - Homer, Adelaide (memorabilia book) (Box 1962.6)
  - Rundlett, Lois (memorabilia book) (Box 1961)
  - Wilder, Katharine Abbott (memorabilia book) (Box 1962)
- Class of 1924 records, 1920-1994; 21.167 linear feet (25 containers)
  The Class of 1924 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1924, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1924 was the forty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  - Commencement, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1920 (Box 1963, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1920-1921 (Box 1963, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1920-1924 (Box 1963, Folder 6)
  - History, 1924; undated (Box 1963, Folder 7)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Day, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 10)
  - Last Chapel, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 11)
  - Last Sing, 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 12)
  - Class Letters, 1934-1989 (Box 1963, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 1923-1924 (Box 1963, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1927-1929 (Box 1963, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 1963, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1939-1944 (Box 1963, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 1963, Folder 18)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1949 (Box 1963, Folder 19)
  - Reunions-Notebook, 1949 (Box 1963, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 1963, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1963, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 1963.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Letters to Reunion Chairmen, 1964 (Box 1963.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Notebook, 1964-1969 (Box 1963.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 1963.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 1963.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 1963.1, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 1963.1, Folder 7)
  - Reunion Scrapbook and Class Scrapbook, 1949; 1922-1924 (Box 1963.5)
  - Reunion Scrapbooks, 1954-1969 (Box 1963.6)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files- Deceased Members A-L (Box 1963.2)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files- Deceased Members M-Z (Box 1963.3)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files, 1924-1994 (Box 1963.4)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 8)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 9)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1963.1, Folder 10)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1922 (Box 1963.1, Folder 12)
  - Step Sings, 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 13)
  - Class Supper, 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 11)
  - Individuals A-Man (Box 1964)
  - Individuals Mar-Sta (Box 1965)
  - Individuals Ste-Z (Box 1966)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight (correspondence, A - S) (Box 1967)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight (correspondence, T-Z and Inscriptions from authors) (Box 1968)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight (manuscript, Guns of Quebec and Mystery of Vanishing Horses) (Box 1969)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight (manuscript, Theodora) (Box 1970)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.6)
  - Fairbanks, Pauline (photo album) (Box 1971.7)
  - Hayden, Pauline Emma (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.8)
  - Mandlebaum, Helen (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.9)
  - Marsh, Beatrice Hubbell (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.10)
  - Pierpont, Grace (scrapbook), 1920-1924; 2017-A-0157; Pierpont, Grace, Class of 1924; Hazard, James P.; .5 linear feet (1 oversize flat box) (Box 1)
    Scrapbook of Grace Pierpont, Class of 1924, as well as family records and copies of "The Campus Cat" (1924)
    Hazard, James P.
  - Present, Ruth (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.11)
  - Present, Ruth (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.12)
  - Richardson, Mary Emmett (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.13)
  - Smith, (Martha) Evelyn (memorabilia book) (Box 1971.14)
  - Unknown (scrapbook) (Box 1971.15)
- Class of 1925 records, 1921-1995; 7.625 linear feet (16 containers)
  The Class of 1925 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1925, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1925 was the forty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  - Commencement, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1921 (Box 1972, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1921-1922 (Box 1972, Folder 6)
  - General, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1921-1925 (Box 1972, Folder 8)
  - History, undated (Box 1972, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom, 1924 (Box 1972, Folder 12)
  - Junior Ushers, 1924 (Box 1972, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1934-1984 (Box 1972, Folder 14)
  - Class Notes, 1966-1975 (Box 1972, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1973, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 1973, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 1973, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 1973, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 1973, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 1973, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 1973, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 1973, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 1973, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 1973, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1970-1980 (Box 1973, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1980-1985 (Box 1973, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1995 (Box 1973, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-Photographs, undated (Box 1973, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Songs, undated (Box 1973, Folder 15)
  - Reunion Costume (Box 1973.1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 16)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 17)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1972, Folder 18)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1923 (Box 1972, Folder 19)
  - Step Sing, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 20)
  - Class Supper, 1925 (Box 1972, Folder 21)
  - Individuals A-G (Box 1974)
  - Individuals H-Low (Box 1975)
  - Individuals Low-Z (Box 1976)
  - Barnard, Lucy (memorabilia book) (Box 1976.2)
  - Crawford, Cheryl (One Naked Individual) (Box 1976.3)
  - Hagler, Marion (correspondence) (Box 1976.1)
  - Hagler, Marian (scrapbooks) (Box 1976.4)
  - Huston, Judelle MacGregor (course notes, personal papers) (Box 1977)
  - Knott, Grania O'Malley (papers from college years, correspondence) (Box 1978)
  - Knott, Grania O'Malley (memorabilia book) (Box 1978.1)
  - Lackey, Anne Lockwood (correspondence) (Box 1979)
  - Lane, Harriet Page (correspondence) (Box 1980)
  - Sebring, Mary (photograph), 1925; 1 items (1 photograph) (Box 1976)
    Donated by Carol D. M. Strasburger, May 2018 (Accession 2018-A-0054).
  - Wheeler, Eunice (photo album) (Box 1980.1)
- Class of 1926 records, 1922-1986; 6.0 linear feet (14 containers)
  The Class of 1926 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1926, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1926 was the forty-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
  - Addresses (Box 1981, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (Box 1981, Folder 2)
  - Commencement (Box 1981, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Chapel Service (Box 1981, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music (Box 1981, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs (Box 1981, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker (Box 1981, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook (Box 1981, Folder 8)
  - General (Box 1981, Folder 9)
  - Groups (Box 1981, Folder 10)
  - Hoop Rolling (Box 1981, Folder 11)
  - Illumination Night (Box 1981, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day (Box 1981, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs (Box 1981, Folder 14)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party (Box 1981, Folder 15)
  - Junior Ushers (Box 1981, Folder 16)
  - Class Letters (Box 1981, Folder 17)
  - Class Member Cards (Box 1981.3)
  - Officers (Box 1981, Folder 18)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 19)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 20)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 21)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 22)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 23)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 24)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 25)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 26)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 27)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 28)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 29)
  - Reunions (Box 1981.1, Folder 30)
  - Reunion Costume (Box 1981.5)
  - Sophomore Carnival (Box 1981.2, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files (Box 1981.4)
  - Senior Dramatics (Box 1981.2, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs (Box 1981.2, Folder 3)
  - Songs and Step Sing (Box 1981.2, Folder 4)
  - Class Supper (Box 1981.2, Folder 5)
  - Yearbook Photographs (Box 1981.2, Folder 6)
  - Individuals A-C (Box 1982)
  - Individuals D-O (Box 1983)
  - Individuals P-Z (Box 1983.1)
  - Clark, Eleanor (Ivy Day Song music sheet) (Box 1984.2)
  - Green, Helen Celeste (photograph album and printed materials), 1926; 2017-A-0152 (Box 1)
  - Jordan, Ruby Mae (correspondence, manuscript) (Box 1984)
  - Neal, Ruby (reunion materials, Rochester Smith Club materials, school art notebook) (Box 1984.1)
  - Simpson, Eva Best (memorabilia book) (Box 1984.2)
  - Winchell, Dorothy, ex-'26 (photo album) (Box 1984.3)
- Class of 1927 records, 1923-2002; 10.896 linear feet (24 containers)
  The Class of 1927 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1927, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1927 was the forty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  - Commencement, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Music, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speech - Rev. Harry Emerson Fosdick, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1923 (Box 1985, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind, 1923 (Box 1985, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1923-1924 (Box 1985, Folder 8)
  - Fund Letters, 1957-1973 (Box 1985, Folder 9)
  - General, 1923-1927 (Box 1985, Folder 10)
  - Groups - Photographs, 1923-1927 (Box 1985, Folder 11)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 14)
  - Last Sing, 1927 (Box 1985, Folder 15)
  - Class Letters, 1929-1992 (Box 1985, Folder 16)
  - Necrology, 1981 (Box 1985, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1928 (Box 1985, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1985, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1932 (Box 1985, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 1985, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1985, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 1985, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 1986, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 1986, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 1986, Folder 3)
  - Reunions - Reunion Chair's Notebook, 1962 (Box 1986, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 1986, Folder 5)
  - Reunions - Reunion Chair's Notebook, 1967 (Box 1987, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 1987, Folder 2)
  - Reunions - Questionnaire, 1972 (Box 1987, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 1987, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 1987, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Box 1987, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 1987, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1997 (Box 1987, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 2002 (Box 1987, Folder 9)
  - Reunions - Memorabilia, undated (Box 1987, Folder 10)
  - Reunions - Photographs, undated (Box 1987, Folder 11)
  - Reunions - Songs, 1932-72 (Box 1987, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, 1947-1955 (Box 1987, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, 1947-1955 (Box 1987.3)
  - Class Secretary's Biographical Notes and Clippings, undated (Box 1987, Folder 14)
  - Secretary's Card Files (A-Z, Deceased A-E) (Box 1985.1)
  - Secretary's Card Files (Deceased F-V) (Box 1985.2)
  - Secretary's Card Files (Deceased W-Z, Ex Members, Lost) (Box 1985.3)
  - Class Secretary's Records, 1927 (Box 1987, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1927 (Box 1987.1, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics - Photographs, 1927 (Box 1987.1, Folder 2)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 3)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1925 (Box 1987.1, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Push, 1925 (Box 1987.1, Folder 5)
  - Step Sings, undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 6)
  - Class Supper, undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 7)
  - Class Treasurer's Records, undated (Box 1987.1, Folder 8)
  - Class Treasurer's Card Files, Class Secretary's Card Files, undated (Box 1987.2)
  - Individuals A-G (Box 1988)
  - Individuals H-L (Box 1988.1)
  - Individuals M-Re (Box 1989)
  - Individuals Ri-Z (Box 1990)